{"Y":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"does the school have a water source?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[8,31.91,23.97,12.68,33.01,38.84,28.57,61.11,13.21,18.18,27],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[92,68.09,76.03,87.32,66.99,61.16,71.43,38.89,86.79,81.82,73],"type":"bar"}]},"EY":{"answer":["Basic","Limited","No Service"],"question":"proportion of schools with basic drinking water from an improved source available at school","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Basic","stack":"2018","data":[77.33,45.74,50.68,63.38,52.43,42.98,58.02,33.33,69.81,65.58,56],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Limited","stack":"2018","data":[5.33,12.77,4.11,9.86,10.68,14.88,7.58,0,5.66,15.58,9],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Service","stack":"2018","data":[17.33,41.49,45.21,26.76,36.89,42.15,34.4,0,24.53,18.83,29],"type":"bar"}]},"EZ":{"answer":["Improved","No Water","Unimproved"],"question":"primary water source (improved or not)","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Improved","stack":"2018","data":[82.67,58.51,54.79,73.24,63.11,57.85,65.6,33.33,75.47,81.17,65],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Water","stack":"2018","data":[10.67,35.11,34.25,18.31,33.98,38.84,30.03,66.67,22.64,18.18,31],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Unimproved","stack":"2018","data":[6.67,6.38,10.96,8.45,2.91,3.31,4.37,0,1.89,0.65,5],"type":"bar"}]},"AN":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"is the water available from the primary water source at the time of the survey?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[21.33,54.26,49.32,36.62,47.57,57.02,41.69,66.67,28.3,34.42,44],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[78.67,45.74,50.68,63.38,52.43,42.98,58.31,33.33,71.7,65.58,56],"type":"bar"}]},"AV":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"does the school have toilets?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[82.67,63.83,55.48,11.27,51.46,71.9,47.52,83.33,79.25,30.52,58],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[17.33,36.17,44.52,88.73,48.54,28.1,52.48,16.67,20.75,69.48,42],"type":"bar"}]},"FB":{"answer":["Basic ","Limited","No Services"],"question":"single-sex basic sanitation toilet","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Basic ","stack":"2018","data":[8,13.83,25.34,57.75,18.45,12.4,23.62,11.11,11.32,26.62,21],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Limited","stack":"2018","data":[5.33,8.51,12.33,30.99,13.59,9.92,10.5,5.56,7.55,14.29,12],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Services","stack":"2018","data":[86.67,77.66,62.33,11.27,67.96,77.69,65.89,83.33,81.13,59.09,67],"type":"bar"}]},"FC":{"answer":["Improved","No Toilet","Unimproved"],"question":"is the sanitation improved?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Improved","stack":"2018","data":[13.33,22.34,37.67,88.73,33.01,22.31,34.69,16.67,18.87,41.56,33],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Toilet","stack":"2018","data":[86.67,77.66,60.27,11.27,58.25,76.86,57.73,83.33,81.13,57.14,65],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Unimproved","stack":"2018","data":[0,0,2.05,0,8.74,0.83,7.58,0,0,1.3,2],"type":"bar"}]},"FD":{"answer":["Accessible","Inaccessible"],"question":"accessibility of sanitation source to students with limited mobility","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Accessible","stack":"2018","data":[16,20.21,32.88,84.51,44.66,21.49,45.48,5.56,15.09,53.25,34],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Inaccessible","stack":"2018","data":[84,79.79,67.12,15.49,55.34,78.51,54.52,94.44,84.91,46.75,66],"type":"bar"}]},"CF":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"are there hand washing facilities at the school?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[81.33,75.53,58.9,25.35,66.02,88.43,81.92,83.33,60.38,91.56,71],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[18.67,24.47,41.1,74.65,33.98,11.57,18.08,16.67,39.62,8.44,29],"type":"bar"}]},"CL":{"answer":["Both soap and water","Soap only","Water only"],"question":"are both soap and water available at the hand washing facility?","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Both soap and water","stack":"2018","data":[0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Soap only","stack":"2018","data":[0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Water only","stack":"2018","data":[50,52.17,81.67,52.83,65.71,85.71,0,0,95.24,61.54,54],"type":"bar"}]},"CR":{"answer":["No","Yes"],"question":"does the school have a changing area where girls can change and wash safely (private and secure, door and lock and hangers)","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"No","stack":"2018","data":[97.33,95.74,93.84,85.92,96.12,97.52,94.46,100,100,92.86,95],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Yes","stack":"2018","data":[2.67,4.26,6.16,14.08,3.88,2.48,5.54,0,0,7.14,5],"type":"bar"}]},"FE":{"answer":["Basic","Limited","No Services"],"question":"handwashing facilities","province":["Central","Choiseul","Guadalcanal","Honiara","Isabel","Makira","Malaita","Rennell and Bellona","Temotu","Western","National"],"result":[{"name":"Basic","stack":"2018","data":[9.33,11.7,7.53,35.21,11.65,1.65,4.96,0,1.89,3.25,9],"type":"bar"},{"name":"Limited","stack":"2018","data":[9.33,12.77,33.56,39.44,22.33,9.92,13.12,0,37.74,5.19,18],"type":"bar"},{"name":"No Services","stack":"2018","data":[81.33,75.53,58.9,25.35,66.02,88.43,81.92,0,60.38,91.56,63],"type":"bar"}]}}